A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Administrative (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 1-2, 1003-1947 (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 3-4, 1003-1947 (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 5, 1003-1947 (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 1-2, 1948-1999 (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 3-4, 1948-1999 (Box 23)
  - Hospital for Joint Disease, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V1, Page 5, 1948-1999 (Box 23)
  - Joseph 3G, Medical Unit, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1 (Box 23)
  - Joseph 3G, Medical Unit, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2 (Box 23)
  - Joseph 3G, Medical Unit, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3 (Box 23)
  - Joseph 3G, Medical Unit, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4 (Box 23)
  - Joseph 3G, Medical Unit, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 23)
  - Kaiser Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 23)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 February (Box 23)
  - OSF, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 February (Box 24)
  - OSF, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 February (Box 24)
  - OSF, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 February (Box 24)
  - OSF, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 February (Box 24)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 24)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 24)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 24)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 24)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 25)
  - Allen Pavillion, Fairview, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 June (Box 25)
  - Dana Farbeth, Mayo Rochester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 25)
  - Overlake, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 25)
  - Overlake, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 25)
  - Overlake, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 25)
  - Mass General Group III, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 25)
  - Mass General Group III, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - Mass General Group III, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - Mass General Group III, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - UTMB, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - UTMB, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - UTMB, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - Dana Farbeth, Mayo Rochester, Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - Dana Farbeth, Mayo Rochester, Post Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 26)
  - Robert Wood, Mayo Rochester, Post Intervention, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2005 November (Box 27)
  - River Valley North, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2005 December (Box 27)
  - River Valley North, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2005 December (Box 27)
  - River Valley North, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2005 December (Box 27)
  - River Valley South, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 27)
  - River Valley South, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 27)
  - River Valley South, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 28)
  - River Valley South, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 28)
  - Robert Wood Johnson, Rahway, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2006 January (Box 28)
  - Robert Wood Johnson, Rahway, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2006 January (Box 28)
  - Kaiser Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Kaiser Pilot, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Kaiser, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Kaiser, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Kaiser, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Kaiser, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 January (Box 29)
  - Saint John, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 March (Box 30)
  - Saint John, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 March (Box 30)
  - Kaiser Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 November (Box 30)
  - Kaiser Pilot, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 November (Box 30)
  - Kaiser Control, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), 2004 November (Box 30)
  - Crozer Chester Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 107000-108000 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, Part 1 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, Part 2 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, Part 1 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, Part 2 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, Part 1 (Box 31)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, Part 2 (Box 32)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, Part 1 (Box 32)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, Part 2 (Box 32)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, Part 1 (Box 32)
  - Englewood Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, Part 2 (Box 32)
  - Florida Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 32)
  - Florida Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 32)
  - Florida Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 32)
  - Florida Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 32)
  - Florida Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 32)
  - DAMS (Diabetic Anemia Management Survey) (Box 33)
  - NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly), Presentation, 2000 July 17 (Box 33)
  - Final NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) Package, 1997 (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP)/NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly), PowerPoint Report Update (Box 33)
  - Verification of Original Databases (Box 33)
  - Database Analysis (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Recodes NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) I & II (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Hospital Administrativer Information (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Factor Analysis (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Data Pack No. 1, 1999 October 26 (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Syntax (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Presentations (Box 33)
  - New York University (NYU) Material, Factor Analysis (Box 33)
  - Re-Analysis, UC (University of California Davis, MetroWest Medical Center, St, Joseph's Mercy-Oakland, University of California Davis, Databsase Comparasion (Box 33)
  - Re-Analysis, UC (University of California Davis, MetroWest Medical Center, St, Joseph's Mercy-Oakland, MetroWest Medical Center, Database Comparasion (Box 33)
  - Re-Analysis, UC (University of California Davis, MetroWest Medical Center, St, Joseph's Mercy-Oakland, St, Joseph's Mercy-Oakland, Database Comparasion (Box 33)
  - Re-Analysis, UC (University of California Davis, MetroWest Medical Center, St, Joseph's Mercy-Oakland, Sound Shore (Box 33)
  - NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) I Site Outcomes Assessment, Patient Record Data Collection Sheet (Box 34)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Confidential Material
  - NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) I Site Outcomes Assessment, Patient Record Data Collection Sheet (Box 34)
  - Riverside Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 34)
  - Riverside Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 34)
  - Riverside Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 34)
  - Riverside Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 34)
  - Riverview Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 34)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 115606-116156 (Box 34)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 116161-116805 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 115606-116157 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 116161-116805 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 115606-116156 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 116157-116805 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 115606-116157 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 116161-116805 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 115606-116157 (Box 35)
  - Rogue Valley Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 116161-116805 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3000-3049 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3000-3049 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3000-3049 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3050-3102 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3050-3102 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3050-3102 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3103-3166 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3103-3166 (Box 35)
  - Rolling Plains, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3103-3166 (Box 35)
  - W. A. Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 1092XX-1099XX (Box 36)
  - W. A. Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 1092XX-1099XX (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 105722-105816 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 105722-105816 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 105722-105816 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 105722-105816 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 105722-105816 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 105817-106183 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 105817-106183 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 105817-106183 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 105817-106183 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 105817-106183 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25114-26877 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 25114-26877 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 25114-26877 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 26878-26956 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 26878-26956 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 26878-26956 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 26960-27036 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 26960-27036 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 26960-27036 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 27037-27099 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 27037-27099 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 27037-27099 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 105538-105652 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 105538-105652 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 105538-105652 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 105538-105652 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 105538-105652 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 105653-105720 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 105653-105720 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 105653-105720 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 105653-105720 (Box 36)
  - Waukesha, Post, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 105653-105720 (Box 36)
  - Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Antwerp (Box 36)
  - Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Antwerp, University of Iowa (Box 36)
  - Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Antwerp, Trinitas Hospital (Box 36)
  - Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Antwerp, Englewood Hospital (Box 36)
  - Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Antwerp, University of North Carolina (Box 36)
  - University of North Carolina (UNC), Chapel Hill (Box 36)
  - NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) (Box 36)
  - Printing, Examples, Top Edge Gluing, Sample (Box 36)
  - Printing, Examples, Inner Edge Gluing, Example (Box 36)
  - NICHE (Nursing Improving Care to Hospitalized Elderly) (Box 36)
  - How To Do the GIAP (Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile) (Box 36)
  - Visiting Nurse Services (VNS) Consulting Agreement (Box 36)
  - GIAP (Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile) Validity Article (Box 36)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100430-100526 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100430-100526 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100430-100526 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100430-100526 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100430-100526 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100527-100694 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100527-100694 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100527-100694 (Box 37)